showme.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy policy - ShowMe Online Learning

Learnbat, Inc. (“ShowMe,” “we,” “us,” “our”), knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting the ShowMe’s website at www.showme.com or any of ShowMe’s other websites, applications, domain names or other linked pages, (collectively the “Website”), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

You post any Content (as that term is defined in the ShowMe’s Terms of Use located at www.showme.com/termsofuse) on the Website at your own risk. Although we may allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Content you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of Content or other information accessible on the Website is a violation of the ShowMe’s Terms of Use and should be reported to info@showme.com.

## WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy explains how ShowMe collects and uses information from its users who access the Website and use our services, including ShowMe’s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"). Also, this Privacy Policy covers ShowMe’s treatment of any Personal Information that ShowMe’s business partners share with ShowMe, or that you provide to the ShowMe through a third party website using a ShowMe application. This policy does not apply to websites or practices of companies that ShowMe does not own or control, or to individuals that ShowMe does not employ or manage.

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES SHOWME DISPLAY OR COLLECT?

When you use the Website, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, and transmit information through various channels, as permitted by the functionality of the Website. The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our services, and, in some cases, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile through the Website. In most cases, we retain such information so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your connections list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. Specifically, we collect the following types of information from our users.

### Information You Provide to Us:

##### Children’s Personal Information:

ShowMe collects limited information from individuals under the age of 13 (“child” or “children”). During registration, we collect full name, a username, password, email address, birthday, location, a parent's e-mail address and one or more ShowMe interactive whiteboard presentation(s). We consider the full name and email address, as well as any other individually identifiable information about an individual under the age of 13 which we collect online, to be “Children’s Personal Information”. We review the usernames and ShowMe’s for Children’s Personal Information and for any objectionable or inappropriate content. If there is none, we make the ShowMe’s public along with the child’s username.

We then request parental approval for the registration and for the collection of additional information from the child by sending an email to the provided parent’s email address. We will then display the child’s city and state along with the child’s ShowMes. We never disclose Children’s Personal Information to third parties.

If the parent decides to cancel the child’s registration, they may do so at any time. If the parent cancels the registration, we will delete all the information that the child has provided to us, and the child will not be permitted to use certain features of the ShowMe site.

If you are a child, you may not send any Children’s Personal Information about yourself to us, other than what we request from you when you sign up for the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected Children’s Personal Information from a student without parental consent, or if we learn a student has provided us Children’s Personal Information beyond what we requested during registration for the Website (i.e. full name and email address), we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child may have provided us Children’s Personal Information beyond what is requested when signing up for the Website, or that a child has not obtained parental consent, please contact us at info@showme.com.

##### Information Provided by Users Age 13 and Older:

We receive and store any information you knowingly enter on the Website, whether via computer, mobile phone, other wireless device, or that you provide to us in any other way. This information may include your name, email address, birthday, password, school affiliation, friend lists, teacher’s name, location, photo, bio and any other information necessary for us to provide our services (“Personal Information”). You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of one or more of our features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain information, products and services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new features. You may modify or remove your Personal Information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features to edit your profile and/or account information.

### Information Collected Automatically:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Website or our services. ShowMe automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, ShowMe cookie information, and the page you requested. We also record the details of your activity on the Website. This information is not Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information.

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. ShowMe only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use our partners' services and the Website to help provide you with an optimal online experience.

##### Email Communications:

If you provide us your email address, we may send you email communications. If you are a child, we will only use your email address to send you notifications and newsletters. If you are not a child, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from ShowMe if your computer supports this type of program. ShowMe uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. We also compare our non-child user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users.

##### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. ShowMe cookies do not collect Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because you will not be able to log in or use many of the Website’s most attractive features without cookies enabled.

## WILL SHOWME SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. However, we share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form as described below.

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Website (either alone or jointly with us). We may, for example, sell products or provide services jointly with affiliated businesses, or work with third party websites to enhance your online experience. These transactions or services may or may not be commercial in nature. You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. Such services may include the ability for you to automatically transmit information you input on the Website to your profile or account on a third party website, or to automatically transmit information you input on a third party website to your Website profile. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to allow the automatic transmissions discussed above, please review all third party websites’ policies before disclosing any Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information or other content on the Website or on any third party website.

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending email, analyzing data, and providing user services. Unless we tell you differently, ShowMe’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

User Profiles: You may choose to populate your user profile on the Website with Personal Information, including, without limitation, your name, photograph, and school affiliation. This user profile information will be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Website or facilitate interaction with the ShowMe. However, please keep in mind that information (whether Personal Information or not) or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others, in accordance with the privacy settings you select in your account preferences. Your user name may be displayed to other users when you upload images or videos or send messages through the Website and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Any images, captions or other content that you submit to the Websites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

Communication About the Website or in Response to User Requests: As part of the Website and our services, you may receive from ShowMe email or other types of communication relating to your use of the Website or your user profile. You acknowledge and agree that by posting information on the Website or otherwise using the Website, ShowMe and its agents may send you email, contact you or engage in other communication that they determine in their sole discretion relate to your profile or use of the Website. If you disclose your email address to ShowMe we may use it to send updates, a newsletter or other news regarding the Website or ShowMe services, or to simply send notifications or newsletters.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if ShowMe, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that ShowMe goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of ShowMe may continue to use your Personal Information and Children’s Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of ShowMe and Others: We may release Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of ShowMe, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be given the option to prevent the sharing of this information. We make sure that all third parties we share data with follow the same privacy and security practices we do as laid out in our policies.

Children’s Personal Information: Other than as stated above, we never share Children’s Personal Information with any third parties.

## IS INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?

Your ShowMe account, Personal Information and/or Children’s Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You may help protect against unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

ShowMe endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, ShowMe cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. For additional information about the security measures ShowMe uses in connection with the Website, please contact us at info@showme.com.

The Website contains links to other sites. ShowMe is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Website. Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post information to public areas on the Website or any other public forums, such information can be accessed by the public.

## WHAT INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

ShowMe allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list may change as the Website changes. You may currently access the following information:

  * information in your user profile,
  * user connections list,
  * user preferences, and
  * photographs and content in your account.

## WHAT OTHER CHOICES DO I HAVE?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain ShowMe features.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Information Can I Access” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Certain types of communication you send to other users cannot be removed, such as messages.

You may request deletion of your ShowMe account by emailing info@showme.com. Please note that after 30 days we will automatically delete all data associated with deleted accounts. Teachers and school administrators who have created student accounts also may request deletion of their students ShowMe accounts by emailing info@showme.com. Further, information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent that it was copied or stored by other users. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you delete your information, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

If you do not wish to receive email or other communications or notifications from us, please email us at info@showme.com. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

ShowMe may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information or Children’s Personal Information, we will notify you via email and by posting an announcement on the Website. You will have the choice to consent to the new changes. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

## QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at ShowMe or www.showme.com, please send us a detailed message to info@showme.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

ShowMe is a proud signatory of the [Student Privacy Pledge.](https://studentprivacypledge.org/)

Effective: May 8, 2018
